As I was coming up with my elevator pitch during my career change,
Ao criar meu "elevator pitch" para a mudança de área,
I kept thinking about two things.
pensei em duas coisas:
One, what did I want employers to know about me?
o que eu queria que o empregador soubesse sobre mim
And two, what was I most proud of?
e o que me deixava mais orgulhoso.
I wanted employers to know that I'm passionate about education, but
Eu queria que eles soubessem da minha paixão por educação,
I wanted them to know I worked hard to get where I was then and
Eu queria que eles soubessem que trabalhei duro
that I was worth taking a chance on.
e que eu merecia uma chance,
Because if I got the job, I would give it everything I had.
pois, se conseguisse a vaga, eu me dedicaria.
So my elevator pitch ended up being something like this.
Então o meu elevator pitch ficou mais ou menos assim:
Hi, I'm Chris,
"Olá, eu sou Chris,
a Full Stack Software Engineer who loves building education products.
um programador que adora criar produtos para educação.
I recently developed a web app using AngularJS that let's teachers share
Desenvolvi um aplicativo na web usando AngularJS
I'd love to combine my passion for
Busco unir a paixão pela educação
teaching and learning with my software development skills to
com minhas habilidades em programação,
continue building personalized learning products for people.
para construir produtos de aprendizado personalizado."
My elevator pitch isn't something I recite when I meet someone.
Meu elevator pitch não é algo que recito para qualquer um.
That would be weird to say hi and then just dive into the pitch, however,
Seria estranho dizer "oi" e já falar o meu discurso,
I could write this pitch as my LinkedIn summary.
mas eu poderia escrevê-lo na apresentação do meu LinkedIn.
When I'm talking to someone,
Quando converso com alguém,
I communicate the points in my pitch throughout the conversation.
expresso esses pontos ao longo da conversa.
Let me show you what that looks like.
Vou mostrar como isso funciona.
Pretend in the next video that Trinh's a recruiter and
Imagine, no próximo vídeo, que Trinh está recrutando,
I'm a job-seeker meeting her at a mixer for education start-ups.
e eu busco uma oportunidade em um encontro de startups.